flashbangstudios.com 2007-02-25

# Flashbang Studios Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

Flashbang Studios takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. This policy may change from time to time, so please check back periodically.

### What information do we collect, and why?

Flashbang Studios collects information in several ways depending on whether you are playing single player games, multiplayer games, or chatting. In most cases, this information is purely voluntary. Flashbang Studios' main goal for collecting this information is to provide you with customized content on our site that is of interest to you.

### What are "Cookies" and how do we use them?

Cookies are small files written on your computer that are only accessible by the FlashbangStudios.com website. The cookie is used for your convenience. For instance, there's no point in showing you an advertisement for a game you've already purchased.

Any information we collect will be stored and processed in a database that resides solely in the United States. 

### Do we share your information with others?

Flashbang Studios does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested or when we have your permission. In addition, we provide you the opportunity to opt-in to receive communications from Flashbang Studios to learn more about new games and promotions.

### Conditions of Use

Your access and use of this site is subject to this Privacy Policy. You may view this policy at any time by visiting [www.flashbangstudios.com/privacy/](http://www.flashbangstudios.com/privacy/)

### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information by Flashbang Studios as stated in this Privacy Policy.

### Opt-In/Opt-Out

Flashbang Studios may automatically send you an email confirmation if you purchase a game from Flashbang Studios or re-license the game. Flashbang Studios will only send additional email communications to you if you give us permission to do so.

Flashbang Studios uses a double opt-in policy for newsletter subscriptions and only sends newsletters to those who opt-in to subscribe. If you are currently a Flashbang Studios newsletter subscriber and would like to terminate your subscription, you may do so by:

\- Clicking on the unsubscribe link at the bottom of the newsletter  
\- By sending mail to the following address: 

> Flashbang Studios  
>  Attn: Opt-Out  
>  6507 S Hardy Drive #214  
>  Tempe, AZ 85283 

### Contacting the Site

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy or the Site, please contact:

> Flashbang Studios  
>  Attn: Privacy  
>  6507 S Hardy Drive #214  
>  Tempe, AZ 85283
> 

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

Flashbang Studios reserves the right to change this privacy policy without notice. Therefore, please check back periodically for any changes.

### Other Web Sites

Other companies that advertise on our site may collect information about you when you view or click on their site or logos. Flashbang Studios is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites. You are encouraged to check the privacy policies of these other sites.

### Other Cookies

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your computer.

### Third-Party Advertising

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

[Mystery Case Files: Ravenhearst, Dream Day Wedding, Virtual Villagers 2: The Lost Children and Chicken Chase Game Downloads](http://www.flashbangstudios.com/)  
About Flashbang Studios | Terms/Privacy | [Unity](http://www.unity3d.com/) | Site Map | [Physics Games](http://www.fun-motion.com/)
